Guide to the Michael Francis Blake Photographs, 1912-1934
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Michael Francis Blake Photographs, 1912-1934, (1 box)
  - Snapshot, adult male standing by a house, unidentified, undated. Mounted photograph., MFB112; 4 x 6 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, adult female, unidentified, undated. Mounted photograph identified as by Blake, 12 W. Sumter., MFB113; 5 x 7; Stamped with Blake's studio address: "M.F. Blake View Photographer 12 W. Sumter Street. Phone 1341-L, Charleston, S.C." (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, adult male, unidentified, undated. Mounted photograph identified as by Blake, 384 W. Sumter., MFB114; 5 x 7; Stamped with Blake's studio address: "M. F. Blake Night and Day Photographer 384 W. Sumter Street, Charleston, S.C." (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, seated adult male between 2 young adult males holding rifles and a young male child in front of them, unidentified, undated. Mounted photograph identified as by Blake, 12 W. Sumter., MFB115; 5 x 7; Stamped with Blake's studio address: "M.F. Blake View Photographer 12 W. Sumter Street. Phone 1341-L, Charleston, S.C." (Box 1)
  - Snapshot, seated elderly male adult holding a cane in a doorway, unidentified, undated. Mounted photograph., MFB116; 5 x 7 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, group of uniformed nurses, possibly a class picture of nurses or nursing students at the Hospital and Training School for Nurses, Charleston, S.C., unidentified, undated. Mounted photograph identified as by Blake, 384. W. Sumter. Possibly an albumen print., MFB117; 5 x 7; Stamped with Blake's studio address: "M. F. Blake Night and Day Photographer 384 W. Sumter Street, Charleston, S.C." (Box 1)